Guide to the Jerome New Frank Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- UNITED STATES COURT OF APPEALS FOR THE SECOND CIRCUIT (CA II), 1941-1957; Series V; 22.5; (54 boxes)
  - Opinions
    - USA ex rel. Walther v. District Director of Immigration and Naturalization, No. 263 (1949 Jun 6) (Box 90, Folder 697)
    - USA ex rel. Watts v. Shaughnessy, No. 277 (1953 May 11) (Box 90, Folder 698)
    - United States Realty and Improvement Company, In re, No. 171 (1946 Feb 4) (Box 90, Folder 699)
    - Upson v. Otis, No. 267 (1946 Apr 1) (Box 90, Folder 700)
    - Usatorre v. M/T Victoria, Compania Argentina de Navegacion Mihanovich Ltda., No. 120 (1948 Nov 29), 1949 (Box 90, Folder 701)
    - Venides v. United Greek Shipowners Corporation, No. 273 (1948 May 31) (Box 90, Folder 702)
    - Vermont Structural Slate Company, Inc. v. Tatko Brothers Slate Company, Inc., No. 313 (1956 Apr 2) (Box 90, Folder 703)
    - Virgin Islands Corporation, The v. W. A. Taylor & Company, No. 59 (1952 Nov 3), 1953 (Box 90, Folder 704)
    - Wabash Corporation, et al. v. Ross Electric Corporation, et al., No. 21 (1950 Oct 9) (Box 90, Folder 705)
    - Waldie v. Tug Peter C.Gallagher, No. 135 (1941 Dec 8), 1942 (Box 90, Folder 706)
    - Wallace v. United States of America, No. 219 (1944 Jan 31) (Box 90, Folder 707)
    - Walling v. Brooklyn Braid Co., Inc., No. 74 (1945 Oct 8) (Box 90, Folder 708)
    - Walling v. Richmond Screw Anchor Co., Inc., No. 186 (1946 Feb 4) (Box 90, Folder 709)
    - Walling v. The Connecticut Company, No. 221 (1946 Mar 11) (Box 90, Folder 710)
    - Walling v. Twyeffort, Inc., No. 127 (1946 Dec 2), 1947 (Box 90, Folder 711)
    - Walton v. Arabian American Oil Company, No. 291 (1956 Mar 12) (Box 90, Folder 712)
    - Warren v. United States of America, No. 45 (1949 Dec 5) (Box 90, Folder 713)
    - Waterman, Estate of v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 95 (1952 Jan 7) (Box 90, Folder 714)
    - Waterman, et al. v. The Aakre, et al., No. 344 (1941 Jun 9) (Box 90, Folder 715)
    - Weilbacher v. J. H. Winchester & Co., Inc. No. 215 (1952 Apr 14) (Box 90, Folder 716)
    - Weis and Company v. Brannan, No. 39 (1948 Oct 11) (Box 90, Folder 717)
    - Weisser v. Mursam Shoe Corporation, No. 238 (1942 Mar 23) (Box 90, Folder 718)
    - Wende v. McManigal, No. 221 (1943 Apr 5) (Box 90, Folder 719)
    - Wessels v. The Asturias, No. 182 (1942 Feb 2) (Box 90, Folder 720)
    - West India Fruit & Steamship Co., Inc. v. Seatrain Lines, Inc., No. 81 (1948 Oct 11) (Box 90, Folder 721)
    - Westchester County Park Commission v. United States of America, No. 316 (1944 May 22) (Box 90, Folder 722)
    - Western Assurance Company v. Genesee Valley Trust Company, No. 40 (1948 Nov 8) (Box 90, Folder 723)
    - Whitman v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 117 (1949 Dec 5) (Box 90, Folder 724)
    - Wieder v. Isbrandtsen Company, Inc., No. 108 (1950 Dec 11), 1951 (Box 90, Folder 725)
    - Williams v. Green Bay and Western Railroad Company, No. 207 (1945 Jan 8) (Box 90, Folder 726)
    - Williams v. McGowan, No. 81 (1945 Nov 12) (Box 90, Folder 727)
    - Willis v. The Pennsylvania Railroad, No. 338 (1941 Jun 9) (Box 90, Folder 728)
    - Willis v. Weil Pump Company, No. 226 (1955 Mar 14) (Box 90, Folder 729)
    - Willoughby Camera Stores, Inc. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 117 (1942 Jan 12) (Box 90, Folder 730)
    - Wilson and Edwards v. Kraemer, No. 234 (1951 Apr 30) (Box 90, Folder 731)
    - Wilson v. United States of America, No. 115 (1955 Nov 14), 1956 (Box 90, Folder 732)
    - Witmark (M.) & Sons v. Fred Fisher Music Co., No. 123 (1941 Dec 8), 1942 (Box 90, Folder 733)
    - Wood v. United States of America, Nos. 224-225 (1954 May 3) (Box 90, Folder 734)
    - Woolworth (F. W.) Company v. National Labor Relations Board, No. 276 (1941 May 12) (Box 90, Folder 735)
    - York v. Guaranty Trust Company of New York, No. 256 (1944 Jan 31) (Box 91, Folder 736)
    - Young Realty Company v. Darling Stores Corporation, No. 232 (1942 Mar 23) (Box 91, Folder 737)
    - Zalkind v. Scheinman, No. 94 (1943 Nov 1) (Box 91, Folder 738)
    - Zamora, Trustee v. Goldblatt and Moraes Construction Co., Inc., No. 153 (1953 Jan 5) (Box 91, Folder 739)
    - Zell v. American Seating Company, No. 30 (1943 Oct 11) (Box 91, Folder 740)
    - Zipser v. Ewing, No. 226 (1952 May 12) (Box 91, Folder 741)
    - Zirn and Cohen v. The Hanover Bank, No. 259 (1954 Jun 7) (Box 91, Folder 742)
  - Conference Memoranda
    - The following is a key to the abbreviations used in this section: (Box 91, Folder 742)
      ACC --- Alfred C. Coxe (1880-1957)
      ALS --- Austin L. Staley (1902-1978)
      ANH --- Augustus Noble Hand (1869-1954)
      CCH --- Carroll Clark Hincks (1889-1964)
      CCS --- Charles C. Simons (1876-1964)
      CEC --- Charles Edward Clark (1889-1963)
      CGG --- Clarence G. Galston (1876-1964)
      CM --- Calvert Magruder (1893-1968)
      EAE --- Evan A. Evans (1876-1948)
      FF --- Felix Frankfurter (1882-1965)
      HBC --- Harrie Brigham Chase (1889-1969)
      HFG --- Herbert F. Goodrich (1889-1962)
      HRM --- Harold R. Medina (1888-)
      HWG --- Henry W. Goddard (1876-1955)
      JCH --- Joseph C. Hutcheson, Jr. (1879-1973)
      JEL --- Joseph Edward Lumbard (1901-)
      JMH --- John M. Harlan (1899-1971)
      JNF --- Jerome New Frank (1889-1957)
      LH --- Learned Hand (1872-1961)
      PW --- Peter Woodbury (1899-1970)
      SRW --- Sterry Robinson Waterman (1901-1984)
      SWB --- Stephen W. Brennan (1893-1968)
      TWS --- Thomas Walter Swan (1877-1975)
      WHH --- William H. Hastie (1904-1976)
    - Cases heard week commencing May 12 (LH, JNF, HBC), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 743)
    - Motions heard week commencing May 12 (LH, JNF, HBC), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 744)
    - Cases … May 19 (JNF), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 745)
    - Motions … June 2, 1941 (Box 91, Folder 746)
    - Cases … June 9 (TWS, JNF, CEC, LH) [1 of 2 folders], 1941 (Box 91, Folder 747)
    - Cases … June 9 (TWS, JNF, CEC, LH) [2 of 2 folders], 1941 (Box 91, Folder 748)
    - Motions … June 9 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 749)
    - Cases … June 16 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 750)
    - Cases … October 20 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 751)
    - Motions … October 20 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 752)
    - Cases … November 3 (JNF, LH, CEC), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 753)
    - Motions … November 3 (JNF, LH, CEC), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 754)
    - Case … November 10 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1941 (Box 91, Folder 755)
    - Cases … December 8 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1941 (Box 92, Folder 756)
    - Motions … December 8 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1941 (Box 92, Folder 757)
    - Cases … January 12 (JNF, ANH, TWS, HBC), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 758)
    - Motions … January 12 (JNF, ANH, TWS, HBC), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 759)
    - Cases … February 2 (JNF, LH, HBC, CEC), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 760)
    - Motions … February 2 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 761)
    - Cases … March 23 (JNF, GEC, ANH), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 762)
    - Motions … March 23 (JNF, CEC), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 763)
    - Cases heard week commencing April 6 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 764)
    - Motions heard week commencing April 6 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 765)
    - Cases … May 4 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 766)
    - Motions … May 4 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 767)
    - Cases … June 8 (JNF, HBC, TWS), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 768)
    - Cases … June 15 (JNF, CEC, HBC), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 769)
    - Motions … June 15 (JNF, CEC, TWS), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 770)
    - Cases … July 27 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1942 (Box 92, Folder 771)
    - Cases … October 19 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1942 (Box 93, Folder 772)
    - Motions … October 19 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1942 (Box 93, Folder 773)
    - Cases … November 2 (JNF, LH, CEC), 1942 (Box 93, Folder 774)
    - Motions … November 2 (JNF, LH, CEC), 1942 (Box 93, Folder 775)
    - Cases … December 14 (JNF, CEC, ANH), 1942 (Box 93, Folder 776)
    - Motions … December 14 (JNF, CEC, ANH), 1942 (Box 93, Folder 777)
    - Cases … January 11 (JNF, ANH, TWS, LH), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 778)
    - Motions … January 11 (JNF, ANH, TWS), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 779)
    - Cases … February 1 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 780)
    - Motions … February 1 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 781)
    - Cases … March 8 (JNF, ANH, LH), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 782)
    - Motions … March 22, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 783)
    - Cases … April 5 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 784)
    - Motions … April 5 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 785)
    - Cases … May 3 (JNF, CEC, TWS), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 786)
    - Motions … May 3 (JNF, CEC, TWS, LH), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 787)
    - Cases heard week commencing June 14 (JNF, ANH, LH), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 788)
    - Motions heard week commencing June 14 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1943 (Box 93, Folder 789)
    - Cases … June 21 (JNF, LH, CEC), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 790)
    - Motions … June 21 (LH), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 791)
    - Motions … October 4 (JNF, HBC), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 792)
    - Cases … October 11 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 793)
    - Motions … October 11 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 794)
    - Cases … October 18 (JNF, TWS, ANH), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 795)
    - Motions … October 18 (JNF, TWS, ANH), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 796)
    - Cases … November 1 (JNF, CEC, LH, TWS), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 797)
    - Case … November 8 (JNF, HBC), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 798)
    - Cases … December 13 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 799)
    - Motions … December 13 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1943 (Box 94, Folder 800)
    - Cases … January 10 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1944 (Box 94, Folder 801)
    - Motions … January 10 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1944 (Box 94, Folder 802)
    - Cases … January 31 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1944 (Box 94, Folder 803)
    - Cases … January 31 [York v.Guaranty Trust Company, only] (JNF, LH, ANH, CEC), 1944 (Box 94, Folder 804)
    - Motions … January 31 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1944 (Box 94, Folder 805)
    - Cases … March 6 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 806)
    - Motions … March 6 (JNF, HBC, CEC, LH, ANH), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 807)
    - Case … March 27 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 808)
    - Motions … March 27 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 809)
    - Cases … April 10 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 810)
    - Motions heard week commencing April 10 (JNF, CEC, HBC, TWS), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 811)
    - Cases heard week commencing May 1 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 812)
    - Motions … May 1 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 813)
    - Cases … May 22 (JNF, TWS, LH), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 814)
    - Motions … May 22 (JNF, TWS, LH), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 815)
    - Cases … June 12 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 816)
    - Motions … (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1944 (Box 95, Folder 817)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1940, 1941 (Box 95, Folder 818)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1941, 1941-1942 (Box 95, Folder 819)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1942, 1942-1943 (Box 95, Folder 820)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1943, 1943-1944 (Box 95, Folder 821)
    - Cases … October 16 (JNF, ANH, TWS), 1944 (Box 96, Folder 822)
    - Motions … October 16 (JNF, ANH, TWS), 1944 (Box 96, Folder 823)
    - Cases … November 6 (JNF, TWS, CEC, HBC, LH), 1944 (Box 96, Folder 824)
    - Motions … November 6 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1944 (Box 96, Folder 825)
    - Cases … November 13 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1944 (Box 96, Folder 826)
    - Motions … November 13 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1944 (Box 96, Folder 827)
    - Cases … December 11 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1944 (Box 96, Folder 828)
    - Motions … December 11 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1944 (Box 96, Folder 829)
    - Cases … January 8 (JNF, HBC, JCH), 1945 (Box 96, Folder 830)
    - Motions … January 8 (JNF, HBC, JCH), 1945 (Box 96, Folder 831)
    - Case … January 15 (JNF, CEC, CCS), 1945 (Box 96, Folder 832)
    - Cases heard week commencing February 12 (JNF, EAE, CEC), 1945 (Box 96, Folder 833)
    - Motions heard week commencing February 12 (JNF, EAE, CEC), 1945 (Box 96, Folder 834)
    - Cases … March 5 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1945 (Box 96, Folder 835)
    - Motions … March 5 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1945 (Box 96, Folder 836)
    - Cases … April 2 (JNF, HBC, LH), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 837)
    - Motions … April 2 (JNF, HBC, LH), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 838)
    - Cases … May 14 (JNF, HBC, TWS, LH), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 839)
    - Motions … May 14 (HBC), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 840)
    - Cases … June 4 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 841)
    - Motions … June 4 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 842)
    - Case … June 11 (JNF, ANH, TWS), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 843)
    - Motion … June 11 (TWS, HBC), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 844)
    - Motions … July 9 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 845)
    - Cases … October 8 (JNF, HBC, LH), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 846)
    - Motions … October 8 (JNF, HBC, LH), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 847)
    - Cases … November 12 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 848)
    - Motions … November 12 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 849)
    - Cases … December 10 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 850)
    - Motions … December 10 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1945 (Box 97, Folder 851)
    - Cases … January 7 (JNF, CEC, LH, ANH), 1946 (Box 97, Folder 852)
    - Motions … January 7 (JNF, CEC, LH), 1946 (Box 97, Folder 853)
    - Cases … February 4 (JNF, HBC, LH), 1946 (Box 97, Folder 854)
    - Motions … February 4 (JNF, HBC, LH, 1946 (Box 97, Folder 855)
    - Cases … February 11 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 856)
    - Motions heard week commencing February 11 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 857)
    - Cases heard week commencing March 11 (JNF, CEC, LH), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 858)
    - Motions … March 11 (JNF, CEC, LH), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 859)
    - Cases … April 1 (JNF, TWS, LH), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 860)
    - Motions … April 1 (JNF, TWS, LH), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 861)
    - Cases … May 13 (JNF, CEC, HBC), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 862)
    - Motions … May 13 (JNF, CEC, HBC), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 863)
    - Cases … June 10 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 864)
    - Motions … June 10 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 865)
    - Cases … October 7 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 866)
    - Motions … October 7 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 867)
    - Cases … November 4 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 868)
    - Motions … November 4 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1946 (Box 98, Folder 869)
    - Cases … December 2 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1946 (Box 99, Folder 870)
    - Motions … December 2 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1946 (Box 99, Folder 871)
    - Cases … January 13 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 872)
    - Motions … January 13 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 873)
    - Cases … February 3 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 874)
    - Motions … February 3 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 875)
    - Cases … March 10 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 876)
    - Motions … March 10 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 877)
    - Cases… April 7 (JNF, HBC, ANH), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 878)
    - Motions … April 7 (JNF, HBC, ANH), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 879)
    - Cases … May 5 (JNF, TWS, ANH, LH), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 880)
    - Motions heard week commencing May 5 (JNF, TWS, ANH LH), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 881)
    - Cases heard week commencing June 2 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 882)
    - Cases … June 2 [Alaska Pacific Salmon Co, v. Reynolds Metal Co. only] (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 883)
    - Motions … June 2 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1947 (Box 99, Folder 884)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1944, 1944-1945 (Box 100, Folder 885)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1945, 1945-1946 (Box 100, Folder 886)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1946, 1946-1947 (Box 100, Folder 887)
    - Motions … October 13 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1947 (Box 100, Folder 889)
    - Cases … November 10 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1947 (Box 100, Folder 890)
    - Motions … November 10 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1947 (Box 100, Folder 891)
    - Cases … December 1 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1947 (Box 100, Folder 892)
    - Cases … December 8 (JNF, HBC, CEC, LH, ANH), 1947 (Box 100, Folder 893)
    - Motions … December 8 (JNF, HBC, CEC, LH, ANH), 1947 (Box 100, Folder 894)
    - Cases … January 5 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1948 (Box 100, Folder 895)
    - Motions … January 5 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1948 (Box 100, Folder 896)
    - Cases … February 2 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1948 (Box 100, Folder 897)
    - Motions … February 2 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1948 (Box 100, Folder 898)
    - Cases … March 1 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1948 (Box 100, Folder 899)
    - Motions … March 1 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1948 (Box 100, Folder 900)
    - Motion … April 5 (TWS), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 901)
    - Cases heard week commencing April 12 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 902)
    - Motions heard week commencing April 12 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 903)
    - Case … April 26 (JNF), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 904)
    - Cases … May 10 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 905)
    - Motions … May 10 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 906)
    - Cases … May 31 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 907)
    - Motions … May 31 (JNF, ANH, CEC, TWS), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 908)
    - Motion … June 28 (JNF), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 909)
    - Cases … October 11 (JNF, ANH, CEC, LH), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 910)
    - Motions … October 11 (JNF, LH, CEC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 911)
    - Cases … November 8 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 912)
    - Motions … November 8 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 913)
    - Cases … November 29 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 914)
    - Motions … November 29 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 915)
    - Cases … January 10 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1949 (Box 101, Folder 916)
    - Motions … January 10, 1949 (Box 101, Folder 917)
    - Cases … February 14 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1949 (Box 101, Folder 918)
    - Motions … February 14 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1949 (Box 101, Folder 919)
    - Motion … February 28 (JNF, LH), 1949 (Box 101, Folder 920)
    - Cases … March 7 (JNF, LH, TWS, HBC), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 921)
    - Motions … March 7 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 922)
    - Cases … April 4 (JNF, HBC, CEC TWS), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 923)
    - Motions … April 4 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 924)
    - Cases … May 2 (JNF, LH, TWS, ANH), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 925)
    - Motions heard week commencing May 2 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 926)
    - Cases heard week commencing June 6 (JNF, LH, CEC), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 927)
    - Motions … June 6 (JNF, LH, CEC), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 928)
    - Cases … October 10 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 929)
    - Motions … October 10 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 930)
    - Cases … October 31 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 931)
    - Motions … October 31 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 932)
    - Cases … December 5 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 933)
    - Motions … December 5 (LH, TWS), 1949 (Box 102, Folder 934)
    - Cases … January 9 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1950 (Box 102, Folder 935)
    - Motions … January 9 (JNF, ANH, HBC, TWS), 1950 (Box 102, Folder 936)
    - Cases … February 6 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 937)
    - Motions … February 6, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 938)
    - Cases … February 27 (JNF, LH, HFG, CEC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 939)
    - Motions … February 27 (JNF, CEC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 940)
    - Cases … March 6 (JNF, LH, TWS, CEC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 941)
    - Motions … March 6 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 942)
    - Cases … April 3 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 943)
    - Motions … April 3 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 944)
    - Cases … June 5 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 945)
    - Motions … June 5 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 946)
    - Case … June 19, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 947)
    - Motions … June 19 (JNF, ANH, HWG), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 948)
    - Motion … July 17 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 949)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1947, 1947-1948 (Box 103, Folder 950)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1948, 1948-1949 (Box 103, Folder 951)
    - Decisions (list) made by CA II during October Term 1949, 1949-1950 (Box 103, Folder 952)
    - Cases heard week commencing October 9 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 953)
    - Motions heard week commencing October 9 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 954)
    - Cases … October 30 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 955)
    - Motions … October 30 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1950 (Box 103, Folder 956)
    - Cases … December 11 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1950 (Box 104, Folder 957)
    - Motions … December 11 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1950 (Box 104, Folder 958)
    - Cases … January 8 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 959)
    - Motions … January 8 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 960)
    - Cases … February 5 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 961)
    - Motions …February 5 (JNF, LH, TWS), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 962)
    - Cases … February 12 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 963)
    - Cases … March 5 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 964)
    - Motions … March 5 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 965)
    - Cases … March 12 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 966)
    - Cases … April 9 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 967)
    - Motions … April 9, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 968)
    - Cases … April 30 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 969)
    - Motions … April 30 (JNF, LH, HBC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 970)
    - Cases … June 4 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 971)
    - Motions … June 4 (JNF, HBC, CEC, ANH), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 972)
    - Motion heard week commencing June 11 (JNF, TWS), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 973)
    - Motion heard week commencing June 18 (JNF, LH, ANH), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 974)
    - Cases heard week commencing September 10 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 975)
    - Cases … October 1 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 976)
    - Motions … October 1 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 977)
    - Cases … November 5 (JNF, TWS, ACC), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 978)
    - Motions … November 5 (JNF, TWS, ACC), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 979)
    - Motion … December 3 (JNF, ANH, CEC), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 980)
    - Cases … December 10 (JNF, HBC, CEC), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 981)
    - Motions … December 10, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 982)
    - Motion … [December 17?] (JNF), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 983)
    - Cases … January 7 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1952 (Box 105, Folder 984)
    - Motions … January 7 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1952 (Box 105, Folder 985)
    - Cases … February 11 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1952 (Box 105, Folder 986)
    - Motions … February 11 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1952 (Box 105, Folder 987)
    - Cases … March 10 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1952 (Box 105, Folder 988)
    - Motions … March 10 (JNF, TWS, CEC), 1952 (Box 105, Folder 989)
    - Cases … April 14 (JNF, TWS, ANH), 1952 (Box 105, Folder 990)
    - Motions … April 14 (JNF, TWS, ANH, LH), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 991)
    - Cases … May 12 (JNF, ANH, HBC, CEC, TWS), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 992)
    - Motions … May 12, 1952 (Box 106, Folder 993)
    - Cases … June 2 (JNF, ANH, CEC, TWS, HBC), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 994)
    - Motions … June 2 (JNF, ANH, CEC, TWS, HBC), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 995)
    - Cases heard week commencing October 6 (JNF, TWS, LH), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 996)
    - Motions heard week commencing October 6 (JNF, TWS, LH), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 997)
    - Cases … November 3 (JNF, TWS, LH), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 998)
    - Motions … November 3, 1952 (Box 106, Folder 999)
    - Cases … December 8 (JNF, ANH, HBC, CEC), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 1000)
    - Motions … December 8 (JNF, ANH, HBC), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 1001)
    - Case … December 22 (JNF, TWS, HBC), 1952 (Box 106, Folder 1002)